[music]
>> Hello everyone.
Phenomenal. How are you?
Love to hear it. How these past uh
18 hours what have they been like for
you? How much did you sleep last night?
When did you get here today? Yeah, um
you know, they've definitely it's gone
by pretty quickly. It's it's been a bit
of a whirlwind but in the best way
possible, you know, got up this morning
and we're close by, you know, I'm from
Cleveland originally so we just got up
left the house at about 10:00 got to
drive up here and smooth drive like it
was it was awesome. So it was a it was
it was a fast process but it was smooth
nonetheless.
Um honestly I've just been trying to
have gratitude for the moment, you know,
just enjoying the fact that you know, I
get to drive up here and see these
amazing people tour these amazing
facilities, you know, just the the
amount of thankfulness and gratitude
that I have in my heart right now is
incredible.
Excited to be back in the Midwest?
No, it's awesome. It definitely uh it
feels it feels good to be back here, you
know, it feels like home. So With the
football characters
have the driving force in your style
how hard you work, your durability all
that. What what would you say is maybe
the the root of that?
Um you know, I'd really just thank my
parents for that, you know, just seeing
them my whole life, you know, they're
mortgage and real estate agents and
they're working around the clock. Didn't
matter if it was, you know, weekends,
weekdays, late at night, early in the
morning, holidays, like they were around
the clock and they were always
they were always there for their clients
and just kind of seeing the
work ethic that they had and you know,
every every day was working as hard as
you could and I I kind of feel like I
owe it to them to you know, embody that
and try and go even above and beyond.
Last night when we talked to Brad Holmes
he said they had been looking at you for
like 3 years. That's one of those
situations where you never really know
like who's watching you. Like how does
that make you feel when he's saying he
he feels like you've grown ever since
they first began looking at you just
knowing that they have been looking at
you that long and and and they bring you
here now. No, it definitely is really
cool to hear that they've been scouting
me for that long but just kind of
hearing his words of you know, how he
feels I've improved year after year, you
know, obviously every year you you shoot
to improve and to hear his confirmation
on that that you know, he did see
improvement in me year after year and
just
you know, excited too to continue that
mentality and try and get even more and
more technically sound and continue to
improve myself in every way possible to
be the best player I can humanly be. Did
you ever go back and and look at your
freshman year tape at Clemson just out
of curiosity and how much do you feel
like you've grown as a player since
then? Yeah, I mean it'll come up every
so often, you know, we'll have a cut up
or something um and it'll be on there
and you know, it's it's crazy to see,
you know, that that 4 years went by
really really quickly but just kind of
to see where I was then and where I am
now and then just the excitement for you
know, where I'll be
just this time next year like continuing
to get better like that part is super
satisfying to me like the
pursuit of perfection. You also told us
a story. I don't know if you told them
this or you just heard it through the
grapevine that
the way you started playing right tackle
was just because that was the shortest
line you got in. Can you can you tell us
that story? Yeah, so like all throughout
high school I was a left tackle and
you know, I get to Clemson and I look
and the way we did warm-up lines
obviously, you know, we had left tackle,
left guard, center, right guard, right
tackle and like the warm-up line was
whoever was in there and saw that that
line was a little shorter and just kind
of by happenstance hopped in there
started repping there and
you know,
God's grace it worked out for me. Just
wanting to play. That's how it came down
to. Yeah, I just wanted to be you know,
wanted to be available, wanted to get on
the field, wanted to contribute.
They always talk about kind of the
personality of offensive lineman, the
nastiness. You seem pretty soft-spoken.
I'm sure all of this is quite
overwhelming but can you kind of
describe just your mentality on the
field and and where it comes from? Yeah,
you know, I'd say that when I'm
you know, just around people day-to-day,
you know, I'm a pretty even-keeled guy
but when I get out on the field, you
know, I I like to bring some fire and
you know, I try to play with a
competitive edge, you know, there's
there's nothing there's no greater
compliment as an offensive lineman than
you know, quarter one, you know, first
play that guy's super juiced up to come
rush the passer, whatever it might be
and then you see him end of the game and
he's looking for the sideline. Like
that's the ultimate compliment as an
offensive lineman when you can see that.
You shared your first impressions on
Zoom last night about the Lions and what
you see from afar but
were you digging up last night maybe
some more? Did you get texts from
friends of hey you get to play with this
guy? What was your overnight
deep dive into the Lions if there was
one? Yeah, [clears throat] I mean just
continuing to look more and more and I
mean it just it it made me even more
excited, you know, everything I read
made me more excited, you know, just
kind of seeing some clips of coach
Campbell and you know, I already
followed him beforehand but just digging
even deeper now and seeing more and more
of him like I was ready to run through a
wall at you know, midnight last night,
you know, just listening to him talk. So
you know, I'm I'm so fired up to just be
a part of this this team, this
organization. What was your read on the
the Lions throughout the process? What
who did you talk to? What were your
experiences along the way? Yeah, you
know, I got to I got to meet with um
them at the combine and then I got to do
like an interview via Zoom and
you know, I just with every interview
tried to put my best foot forward, learn
as much information as from the person
as I could, you know, everyone does
things a little differently and just
trying to take bits and pieces from
whatever one teaches and you know, coach
Fraley's very intelligent like he was a
great teacher as well like when he was
teaching me some of their stuff like it
was um
you know, it was it was easy to learn
just cuz of how great of a teacher he is
and you know, him having experience too
as a player I feel like that lends it
lends itself well to him being able to
meet you where you are and help you.
You um
but used to run track, you were a state
champion in wrestling. I'm just curious
like it's such a diverse background for
somebody of your size and somebody of
your skill set at this position. How
much of that experience in your
formative years helped shape the way you
approach the game now?
Yeah, I'd say the biggest one that kind
of helped shape me was wrestling, you
know, our wrestling coach was a pretty
no-nonsense guy. He was all about
toughness, all about grit like he'd have
us in the the wrestling room with the
the heat all the way up, you know, 95°
in there running around and you know,
I'm just a little second grader and like
he he preached like
preached not quitting, like preached
toughness and you know, I feel like that
kind of stuck with me, you know, you you
want to be a guy who's tough, you want
to be a guy who has grit, you want to be
a guy who's
you know,
going to finish and not going to crumble
when stuff gets hard. Are you still in
contact with that coach at all? Is is he
still in your life? Uh no, he is not. I
haven't I haven't talked to him but
probably should.
Hey when you when you were watching
clips of Campbell last night were those
old clips of him or those clips of him
talking about you last night? When were
those from?
>> No, it was like old clips of him, you
know, talking to the team, addressing
the team, talking to players, talking
about players, just like everything he
says, you know, gets you fired up. Like
he
you know, you listen to him speak and
you can hear the passion in his voice,
you can hear the care in his voice and
like that that resonates with me and you
know, it it just it gets me fired up
like it gets me ready to go.
Off field, can you give us an idea of
you know, what your hobbies are? Do you
hunt, fish, skydive? What are you what
are you into besides football I guess?
>> I I'd say, you know, just just broad,
you know, being around friends, being
around family um you know, I like to
play golf, like to fish
little bit of video games, watch some TV
with the friends, you know, go out get
some food, you know, whatever. I'm I'm
pretty easy when it comes to that stuff
as long as I'm around people who mean a
lot to me. How did you feel like you
stacked up against the other tackles
that were drafted in the first round as
you went through the pre-draft process?
Um you know, obviously there's a lot of
talented guys in this process and you
know, my biggest thing was just making
sure that I was trying to be the best
version of me every day. You know, I
think uh comparison is the thief of joy.
So just focusing on my process day in
and day out and you know, trying to
be the best I could be and you know, the
guys I was training with trying to make
them better as well. Like that was my
main focus to be honest with you. How
comfortable were you with the idea that
that you know, I guess
you know, throughout your NFL career
you're going to be compared to these
guys I guess and
just just based on
you know, the fact that you guys are all
first rounders.
Yeah, I mean I'd say naturally, you
know, people are going to get compared
to one another but at the end of the day
it all comes back to
you know, trying to excel in whatever
role you're in, you know, trying to be
the best at your game that you can be
because you know, no two people are
going to be the same and everyone has
different strengths and weaknesses but
it's trying to maximize your strengths
personally and minimize your strengths
or minimize your weaknesses I should say
that is really what's going to make you
the best player at least in my opinion.
Like you showed up to the you're now
among kind of a new group of prospect
that's coming through the NIL era. What
allowed you to stay committed to Clemson
and kind of just what was it like kind
of being now in the in the college game
when it looks it's looking a little more
professional? Yeah, um for me like I
never really crossed my mind to
transfer. Um, you know, Coach Sweeney
had a phenomenal program there and, you
know, just the the coaching staff he had
around, you know, Coach Loop, I I had no
it didn't interest me in the slightest.
You know, I felt like those guys had
been faithful and committed to me
throughout my time there and I owed them
to do the same and I was just I was
super happy there. You uh showed up to
the combine surprised some people with
your your makeover, clean-shaven head of
hair. I'm just curious, [clears throat]
what what went into that decision? Do
you think you're going to keep the the
fresh cut? Um, we'll see what happens.
Yeah, you you never know. I'll feel it
out a little bit. I'm liking it now, but
we'll see how I feel here soon. Um, but
I don't know, it just kind of happened,
you know, went wanted to get the hair
cut a little shorter, it was getting in
my face and got cut a little shorter
than I thought it was going to and I was
like, "Oh, well, we're just going to
roll with this." And, you know, I'm
liking it so far, but we'll see. The the
long hair and the beard might make a
return. I'm just curious, uh just
Detroit in general, it's not too far
from where you're at. Um, what's what's
your experience? Have you been to
Detroit before? What do you know about
the city? Uh, it's my first time here. I
just know that, you know, these fans
here really care about their sports,
they're fired up about you know, the
Lions and I I'm just so excited to be a
part of this team and, you know, just
contribute as much as I can and
really make this fan base proud.
The the track, what
what did you participate in? Which
event? I was I was shot put and discus.
So, I guess you should say, you know,
field, but we'll say track and field,
makes me sound a little more athletic.
100?
Um
Go ahead. Uh,
I know you it hasn't even been 24 hours
yet, but have have you talked to any of
your your new teammates yet? Yeah, um,
Penei reached out to me, Tate reached
out to me. It was kind of crazy when um,
I was reading a text and at the bottom
it said Jared Goff. Like, that was a
little surreal moment for me, but, you
know, those guys had reached out and,
you know, just hearing from them and
you know, seeing that they're excited,
you know, it gets me going, gets me
fired up. So, you know, I'm I'm so
excited to, you know, get here in the
building when everyone's here, meet
everyone and get to work. I know you
said you've you've kind of watched
Penei's game a lot. What what did it
mean to get a text from him and, I
guess, what did he say if you you feel
like sharing? Yeah, um, you know,
getting a text from him was the same
thing, it was kind of surreal. Like, you
know, a guy that I'm sitting there, you
know, watching tape on, trying to see
things in his game so I can improve
things in my game and you know, just
just getting a text from him, you know,
saying he's excited for me to be here
and excited to get to work, like,
you know, it it means a lot and I'm just
really excited to, like I said, you
know, when everyone gets here, just
really pick his brain, watch how he
works, try and, you know, glean as much
from him as I humanly can. How how much
do you get the sense that uh
this organization is similar to the
Clemson program that you you came from?
I mean, just values and and the things
that they
um
you know, uh prioritize and then also
like uh how similar do you think, you
know, Dan is to to Dabo? Yeah, um, you
know, I'd say that there is a lot of
similarity just in terms of, you know,
they
really
value toughness, they value finish, they
value grit. Like, I think that was
something that was emphasized to me when
I was in college and that's something,
like, just being here today that I've
heard a lot and it really you know,
resonates with me and that's something
that's near and dear to me. So, I'm
you know, that gets me excited. Um
I just you know, can't say enough good
things about Coach Sweeney and can't say
enough good things about Coach Campbell.
Like, they're two guys who very
obviously care a lot about their
players, very passionate about what they
do. You know, they get fired up when the
time calls for it. Like, they just, you
know, they're two incredible coaches.
What's your favorite What's your
favorite run play when it's called in
the huddle? Um, probably be wide zone,
you know, you get to run off the ball,
get to go displace people and then get
your back in space.
The uh one of the words that was used to
describe you last night a couple times
was a finisher. Um, I guess, where
does that come like what part of your
game do you think that is? Is that work
ethic? Is that or what is it? Um, I
don't know if there's one specific part.
I mean, to me at the end of the day,
like, it doesn't take any God-given
ability to be a guy who finishes. Like,
it's a it's a mentality, it's a mindset.
And I think that's something that was it
was stressed to me in high school and
then Coach Luke at Clemson like stressed
it a lot. Like,
you would, you know, you'd get called
out if you were the guy who was letting
guys come off blocks. Like, it was it
was expected that you're finishing your
block all the way down the field. You
shouldn't have that, you know, some guys
have the timer in their head. Like, you
shouldn't have that. Like, every play
has a chance to be a huge play as long
as we'll finish our blocks. So, that's
been something that's kind of been
ingrained into me, you know, since high
school.
One more question.
But, just a quick, what time did you get
here today and is that your fam Is that
your What family members are here with
you? Yeah, I got here at like 12:15. Um,
and then I'm here with my mom, my dad,
my girlfriend. So.
What position did your dad play?
You know, funny enough, he was uh soccer
and then he was cross country. So.
All right, thank you, guys. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you, everyone. How'd
you get into football then?
He pushed me into it, yeah.
I'm glad he did.
>> [music]
[music]